hey everyone thank you for listening to
The Grow Your Life podcast my name is
Jared makarkowski and on this podcast I
talk about how coaches can grow their
business and make twenty to forty
thousand dollars per month now today I'm
here to help the beginners this is for
those that maybe you know that coaching
is an opportunity for you
but you just don't know what to coach on
you just don't know what to get started
with you just don't know how to move the
needle forward for you here's what I'm
going to tell you you have so much value
to offer the world
if I was talking to you right now if you
were sitting across me I would say this
you have so much value to offer the
world and and and that's not something
to feel embarrassed about at all maybe
that's the first time you've heard that
from somebody and I get that or maybe
intrinsically you know well if I perform
or do something yeah then I got some
value that way but here's what I want to
tell you
do you have knowledge
and information that you know that other
people don't know that other people
don't have that other people don't have
access to because they haven't had the
same experiences as you
and so I want you to honor that first in
yourself
what experiences do you have that nobody
else has
what have you done in your life that
nobody else has done
I'm talking about the whole planet Earth
I'm talking about the whole world
you've there's things that maybe you've
spent years doing or here's a better
question
what if people
what do people come to you for and ask
for advice on
what do people say that you know or do
better than everybody else
now I'm going to pause here if you've
been beaten up and abused and hurt and
you got people in your life that are
constantly ripping into you and telling
you that you're worthless
hey you need to get new friends
because that ain't healthy to hang
around people that treat you that way
but if you're somebody that spends time
around people that love you and care for
you and stuff like that maybe you're
playing some old patterns in your head
because maybe that was an old life that
you lived
it's time to heal from that and here's
why I say that listen I know I get it
healing takes time
grief takes time mourning the the the
life that we thought we would have
doesn't have a timeline on it
but we want to have a growth mindset and
so what I want to do today is I want to
challenge you if I've sent you this
video it's because I have a passion to
help you get to the next level
personally
if you're listening to this right now
the person who sent it to you has a
passion for you to get to the next level
personally okay and so hey I want to
just encourage you you are amazing you
are incredible and I want you to start
to believe that about yourself
and that has nothing to do with how you
perform that has nothing to do with what
you accomplish
I don't care if that's how you've lived
your life up to this moment in time
I get that
it's time to start seeing the greatness
and just how badass you are yourself
so start the beginning step is to love
yourself and to see your own value that
you have value if you can't see that
you're not going to make money in a
coaching business you're not going to be
able the reason why most people can't
figure out where to start in their
coaching business is they don't think
they have value
they don't think they have
Worth to give to other people
they don't see how what they have inside
of them is marketable
to help others with
and this is what I found more often than
not is that if you're somebody who says
I just don't know what to do
I know that coaching is a way to make
ten thousand twenty thousand thirty
thousand dollars a month in a business
but I just don't know where to start
it's usually always has to do with
what's going on up here and you not
really seeing your value at all
okay and so if you're if that's you
you're saying I don't know where to
start
by loving yourself start by giving
yourself
Grace and the love and the kindness and
the compassion that you give to other
people
now some practical steps are this
here's the truth
if you come from other Industries say
the art industry for instance you know
that people buy art because of its
uniqueness
in the coaching business yes people will
connect with you more because you're
different and you're unique than other
people but in the beginning when you
start you're pretty much just going to
be standing on the shoulders of others I
invite you to stand on my shoulders
because I've gotten to this level to
where I know that if you follow the
systems that I've laid out if you follow
how we help our clients make more money
and reach more clients that you can make
the kind of money that's possible in
this business
so you don't have to struggle wondering
how do I make this work
when you follow the system
but you have to make a decision to
decide
on some niche of coaching
here's what I'm going to tell you in the
beginning
you might not make the kind of money you
want to make most of the people who
actually follow my system
the worst case scenario that they have
is they they end up if making back the
amount of money that they spend on
Advertising right away I I don't ever
see people have a runaway ads budget a
runaway
advertising Bill okay
usually the people who actually launch
and actually follow the system
see they break even and then they can
reinvest that you have complete control
when you're running paid advertising as
to
how much you spent okay and so this the
next stage is we have to decide what are
we going to coach on
what are we going to help people with
what are we going to guide people with
okay
this is why the self-worth debate it's
just it's it's really is the most
important
the the mental limiting beliefs that we
have
are so important and then making a
decision
whatever decision that you make as far
as the topic to coach on
doesn't have to be your Forever decision
you're not locked in for life
a lot of times people start with one
idea and then pivot towards another as
they get feedback from the market
until you're getting feedback from the
market of people that are connecting
with you personally and they're telling
you what problems they have you're just
guessing now we can guess strategically
using tools like chat GPT and Jasper to
actually dive into the mind of our
Target Prospect
you can actually use chat CPT to say
okay if I was to create a coaching
program for art therapy to help people
to to heal after grief like that's a
whole Niche right there that you could
make a million dollars in I know for a
fact
because there are people right now doing
that
okay or maybe you'll show people how to
do certain type of art or how to sell a
certain type of art or things like that
whatever that is that you're going to
start with you have to just start and
you have to start by putting yourself
out there and you have to start by
launching and not letting the worry and
the fear run your life
if you let worry and fear control you if
you let worry and fear dictate
how far you're willing to go or stop you
from even starting
it's the Master and Commander of your
life you might not want to hear that you
probably may have maybe have heard me
say that before and it tweaks your brain
and shuts your brain down
but when you let fear and worry run you
you're going to get fear and worries
reward which is absolutely nothing you
won't take any risks you won't say
anything bold you won't walk with
courage now you might be saying Jeremiah
you don't know what I've been through I
am one of the most courageous people out
there awesome I get that
in this area
you have to step out in Courage
you have to make decisions to put
something out there that you cannot
guarantee how it's going to turn out
from day one
and for whatever reason that you're
unable to do that
have you even launched chat GPT yet to
play around with your Niche to play
around with your offer copy to come up
with ideas for courses that you could
sell
you can type in there map out for me an
eight-week course that I could sell on
Art therapy and dive into those topics
right there have you done that yet
truthfully
I doubt you have
most people who say they can't decide
anything
they haven't even created an account
with chat GPT yet or they haven't even
played around with Bing chat or you.com
which is free
or Jasper which is very low cost and
cost effective to be able to use these
actual artificial intelligence tools to
come up with Incredible ideas it's like
having an entire Think Tank
of marketing Geniuses at your disposal
I've been doing marketing for 20 years
and I would be stupid to try to do it
without AI anymore just it's just
ridiculous at this point
and everybody who starts to use the the
AI they all say the same thing I was
skeptical at first
but it literally was
the key that unlocked everything for me
okay or maybe you've used the AI but
you're
you're not sure
how to build a funnel or launch it maybe
you're embarrassed by that you don't
have to be embarrassed by that you know
when you join our community when you're
in our community you can get help from
anything that you're stuck with I don't
want anybody
to be stuck if you're listening to me
right now on this podcast if you're
listening to me or following me
somewhere you can post questions and ask
me in the comments on my social media
and on my YouTube any questions you have
about your business and I'm there to
answer for you
I am a resource for you to answer now I
don't get into the direct messages and
do that with people
because I just it's just a boundary that
I have I don't go into the DMS of people
that aren't one-on-one coaching clients
but you can post on my social media and
ask questions ain't nothing to be
embarrassed about and when you can
humble yourself enough to get the help
you need instead of
beating yourself up and feeling like
you're not good enough and letting the
self-worth story run you and keep
running you and keep you stuck
amazing things unlocked for you in your
life
okay
so I want to encourage you
start playing around with the AI
start playing around with Squarespace
jump into my client growth accelerator
when we open the doors again
get on the waiting list the client girls
accelerator is incredible because we got
all range of people we got people that
are in there that are asking you know
questions about their domain name all
the way up to Advanced advertising
strategy and everywhere in between
people that are just getting started
worrying about the technical stuff all
the way up to Advanced how to scale and
make seven figures
and the whole Gambit in between there
and it's incredible it's an amazing
community of people just like you that
are working towards their goals get on
the waiting list and jump in when we
open those doors
grow your life everybody we'll talk soon
how's it going